Guide to the Vassar College Alumnae/i Biographical Files (AAVC), circa 1865-2015
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Class of 1929
  - Lesher, Magaret E. (Box 78)
  - Levine, Mollie (Box 78)
  - Lewis, Penelope, [EMPTY] (Box 78)
  - Lockwood, Elizabeth (Box 78)
  - Loewenstein, Edith S. (Box 78)
  - Louis, Adrienne W. (Box 78)
  - Low, Dorothy (Box 78)
  - Lowell, Frances S. (Box 78)
  - Lytle, Dorothy L. (Box 78)
  - MacKenzie, Marion (Box 78)
  - Mann, Adrienne (Box 78)
  - Manning, Mary (Box 78)
  - Martin, Helen A. (Box 78)
  - Matthews, Margaret (Box 78)
  - Maulbetsch, Georgette C. (Box 78)
  - McAllister, Annabelle (Box 78)
  - McAndrews, Catherine (Box 78)
  - McConnon, Kathleen B. (Box 78)
  - McGowin, E. Marian (Box 78)
  - McGuirk, Katherine M. (Box 78)
  - McKnight, Leila L. (Box 78)
  - McKown, Frances V. (Box 78)
  - McPherson, Helen H. (Box 78)
  - Mears, Josephine W. (Box 78)
  - Menge, Amy S. (Box 78)
  - Mercer, Caroline G. (Box 78)
  - Miller, Evelyn (Box 78)
  - Miller, Mary (Box 78)
  - Mills, Mary (Box 78)
  - Miner, Helen M. (Box 78)
  - Mitchell, Elizabeth (Box 78)
  - Morris, Hannah P. (Box 78)
  - Morris, M. Elizabeth (Box 78)
  - Moss, Eleanor H. (Box 78)
  - Mueller, Mary E. (Box 78)
  - Myles, Marjory (Box 78)
  - Nash, Eleanor G. (Box 78)
  - Ott, Mary K. (Box 78)
  - Page, Evelyn T. (Box 78)
  - Parker, Anita G. (Box 78)
  - Parry, Dorothy O. (Box 78)
  - Parry, G. Isabel (Box 78)
  - Partridge, Katherine M. (Box 78)
  - Paul, Josephine F. (Box 78)
  - Payne, Ethel J. (Box 78)
  - Pennock, Helen (Box 78)
  - Penny, Elizabeth C. (Box 78)
  - Pero, Virginia (Box 78)
  - Peterson, Elizabeth (Box 78)
  - Pforzheimer, Louise (Box 78)
  - Pierce, Elizabeth K. (Box 78)
  - Pitney, Elizabeth H. (Box 78)
  - Plum, Alice Katharine, [EMPTY] (Box 78)
  - Pollak, Getrude Carolyn (Box 78)
  - Pope, Magaret M. (Box 78)
  - Pratt, Flora L. (Box 79)
  - Prentice, Madeline (Box 79)
  - Proskauer, Ruth (Box 79)
  - Ramey, Elizabeth H. (Box 79)
  - Ramsey, Christine F. (Box 79)
  - Randall, Eleanor (Box 79)
  - Ransom, Julia K. (Box 79)
  - Raymond, Phyllis (Box 79)
  - Reilly, Virginia C. (Box 79)
  - Remington, Julia P. (Box 79)
  - Rianhard, Elizabeth L. (Box 79)
  - Rice, Dorothy (Box 79)
  - Rice, Marjorie B. (Box 79)
  - Ripley, Beatrice (Box 79)
  - Rittenhouse, Margaret M. (Box 79)
  - Roberts, Anna C. (Box 79)
  - Robinson, Alexina G. (Box 79)
  - Robinson, Elizabeth L. (Box 79)
  - Rorty, Margaret M. (Box 79)
  - Rose, Barbara (Box 79)
  - Rosenthal, Frances E. (Box 79)
  - Roth, Elizabeth R. (Box 79)
  - Rounds, Elizabeth (Box 79)
  - Sagendorph, Helen R. (Box 79)
  - Scarlett, Elizabeth (Box 79)
  - Scott, Ethel C. (Box 79)
  - Scott, Helen F. (Box 79)
  - Scott, Louise E. (Box 79)
  - Scudder, Saidie E. (Box 79)
  - Seaman, Miriam (Box 79)
  - Sheets, Elizabeth M. (Box 79)
  - Sheets, Emily K. (Box 79)
  - Sherman, Louise D. (Box 79)
  - Sherwood, Lois (Box 79)
  - Siegmund, Elizabeth C. (Box 79)
  - Simpson, Mary C. (Box 79)
  - Sims, Adelaide (Box 79)
  - Skinner, Mary F. (Box 79)
  - Slichter, Margaret (Box 79)
  - Sligh, Gertrude E. (Box 79)
  - Smith, Jean C. (Box 79)
  - Smith, Jeanette M. (Box 79)
  - Smith, Ora Jeanette (Box 79)
  - Smith, Lillie Powell (Box 79)
  - Smith, Miriam C. (Box 79)
  - Smith, Nancy L. (Box 79)
  - Spalding, Nancy M. (Box 79)
  - Spock, Anne I. (Box 79)
  - Spock, Elizabeth R. (Box 79)
  - Stanton, Margaret G. (Box 79)
  - Staples, Mary Elizabeth (Box 79)
  - Stein, Elizabeth B. (Box 79)
  - Steinbach, G. Mildred (Box 79)
  - Stewart, Charlotte A. (Box 79)
  - Stilling, Harriette (Box 79)
  - Story, Marian B. (Box 79)
  - Straight, Lois H. (Box 79)
  - Street, Sibyl F. (Box 79)
  - Swain, Clara F. (Box 79)
  - Swain, Margaret G. (Box 79)
  - Taff, Clarice M. (Box 79)
  - Tanner, Alice H. (Box 79)
  - Tarrant, Ruth G. (Box 79)
  - Taylor, Ruth M. (Box 79)
  - Teeter, Lois B. (Box 79)
  - Tenney, Frances G. (Box 79)
  - Thompson, Elizabeth L. (Box 79)
  - Thompson, Helen (Box 79)
  - Thompson, Margaret I. (Box 79)
  - Tilden, Carol (Box 79)
  - Tompkins, Margaret V. (Box 79)
  - Tower, Audrey K. (Box 79)
  - Trevvett, Mary (Box 79)
  - Tucker, Rosalie G. (Box 79)
  - Turner, Ruby (Box 79)
  - Tuttle, Evelyn C. (Box 79)
  - Underwood, Elizabeth B. (Box 79)
  - Van Etten, Mary G. (Box 79)
  - Wagenhurst, Janet (Box 79)
  - Walton, Emily (Box 79)
  - Ward, Alice M. (Box 79)
  - Waring, Mary A. (Box 79)
  - Waterhouse, Catharine L. (Box 79)
  - Weaver, Harriet (Box 79)
  - Weiss, Louise E. (Box 79)
  - West, Helen G. (Box 79)
  - Weston, Cornelia (Box 79)
  - Whaley, Marian S. (Box 79)
  - White, Constance (Box 79)
  - Williams, Elizabeth R. (Box 79)
  - Wilson, Kathryn C. (Box 79)
  - Wilson, Meredith (Box 79)
  - Winslow, Nancy M. (Box 79)
  - Wolcott, Clarissa E. (Box 79)
  - Wolfe, Elizabeth (Box 79)
  - Wood, Georgina (Box 79)
  - Wood, Katherine (Box 79)
  - Woods, A. Elizabeth (Box 79)
  - Wright, Dorothy (Box 79)
  - Zorb, Elizabeth H. (Box 79)
- Class of 1930
  - Abbot, Helene (Box 80)
  - Acheson, Jane (Box 80)
  - Adams, Faith (Box 80)
  - Affeld, Dorothy (Box 80)
  - Agger, Carolyn E. (Box 80)
  - Ahlborn, Sarah H. (Box 80)
  - Alschuler, Marian H. (Box 80)
  - Anderson, C. Elizabeth (Box 80)
  - Anderson, Cornelia M. (Box 80)
  - Ash, Kathryn (Box 80)
  - Atwood, Harriet T. (Box 80)
  - Aubrey, Jane (Box 80)
  - Auchincloss, Katrina (Box 80)
  - Austin, Elizabeth (Box 80)
  - Austin, Mabel B. (Box 80)
  - Bacon, Mary O. (Box 80)
  - Bacon, Mary-Frances (Box 80)
  - Bacon, Sara S. (Box 80)
  - Bancroft, Cornelia H. (Box 80)
  - Barnes, Arlene R. (Box 80)
  - Barnum, Pamela (Box 80)
  - Bates, Frances Corson (Box 80)
  - Beaumont, Elsie P. (Box 80)
  - Bedford, Margaret (Box 80)
  - Beer, Elizabeth (Box 80)
  - Benesova, Jana (Box 80)
  - Bennett, Katharine (Box 80)
  - Bentley, Elizabeth T. (Box 80)
  - Bigelow, Jean M. (Box 80)
  - Blair, Mary (Box 80)
  - Blake, Adelaide (Box 80)
  - Blakely, Elizabeth (Box 80)
  - Bliss, Elizabeth B. (Box 80)
  - Blumer, Mary K. (Box 80)
  - Bonbright, Elizabeth M. (Box 80)
  - Boone, Jane F. (Box 80)
  - Bowman, Mary Jean (Box 80)
  - Bowne, Mary A. (Box 80)
  - Boyle, Elizabeth B. (Box 80)
  - Bradley, Gladys A. (Box 80)
  - Brainerd, Lucy B. (Box 80)
  - Brandon, Constance (Box 80)
  - Brown, C. Lewis (Box 80)
  - Brown, Charlotte A. (Box 80)
  - Brown, Helen A. (Box 80)
  - Brown, Marion F. (Box 80)
  - Browne, Phyllis M. (Box 80)
  - Bruce, Miriam M. (Box 80)
  - Buck, Lucy W. (Box 80)
  - Bunn, Evelyn P. (Box 80)
  - Burlingham, Susan B. (Box 80)
  - Burnett, Beatrice (Box 80)
  - Butler, Jane G. (Box 80)
  - Butler, Virginia W. (Box 80)
  - Butterfield, Julia S. (Box 80)
  - Campbell, Margaret (Box 80)
  - Carl, Dorothy (Box 80)
  - Carman, Elise W. (Box 80)
  - Carnes, Charlotte R. (Box 80)
  - Cate, Dorothea (Box 80)
  - Christy, Caroline (Box 80)
  - Clark, Dorothy (Box 80)
  - Clifford, Helen G. (Box 80)
  - Clift, Evelyn H. (Box 80)
  - Cohen, Ethel (Box 80)
  - Cohn, Raida L. (Box 80)
  - Cole, Catherine D. (Box 80)
  - Collens, Emilie (Box 80)
  - Constant, Constance L. (Box 80)
  - Cosmey, Marion A. (Box 80)
  - Coughlin, Florence Anne (Box 80)
  - Courtice, Irma J. (Box 80)
  - Craig, Isabella P. (Box 80)
  - Crocker, Anne M. (Box 80)
  - Cullen, Mary G. (Box 80)
  - Curtis, Virginia H. (Box 80)
  - Daley, Marie E. (Box 80)
  - Dalzell, Sherwood (Box 80)
  - Davidson, Sarah A. (Box 80)
  - Day, Florence E. (Box 80)
  - Dennen, Elisabeth B. (Box 80)
  - Denton, Georgina K. (Box 80)
  - deLancey, Margaret S. (Box 80)
  - Dickey, Jean C. (Box 80)
  - Dickinson, Martha L. (Box 80)
  - Dixon, Katharine A. (Box 80)
  - Dodge, Dorothea (Box 80)
  - Dodge, Katherine M. (Box 80)
  - Dodge, Sally (Box 80)
  - Donham, Clarissa G. (Box 80)
  - Donovan, Helen (Box 80)
  - Doty, Dorothy W. (Box 80)
  - Drewry, Catherine V. (Box 80)
  - DuBois, Dorothy (Box 80)
  - Dudley, Donaldine (Box 80)
  - Duncan, Dorothy L. (Box 80)
  - Duncan, Ruth (Box 80)
  - Dunlap, Aileen M. (Box 80)
  - Durfee, Dorothy A. (Box 80)
  - Earhart, Elizabeth (Box 80)
  - Ebersbach, Rosalind E. (Box 80)
  - Eckerson, Margaret E. (Box 80)
  - Eisner, Gertrude (Box 80)
  - Elton, Deborah R. (Box 80)
  - Ely, Dorothy F. (Box 80)
  - Emerson, Josephine S. (Box 80)
  - Emlen, Susan T. (Box 80)
  - Fechtig, Louise H. (Box 80)
  - Finch, L. Frances (Box 80)
  - Findlay, Helen T. (Box 80)
  - Fishbough, Florence E. (Box 80)
  - Fison, Barbara B. (Box 80)
  - Fitchen, Margaret (Box 80)
  - Flannery, Cynthia P. (Box 80)
  - Foltz, Barbara L. (Box 80)
  - Forest, Lydia M. (Box 81)
  - Fort, Barbara (Box 81)
  - Fowler, Margaret (Box 81)
  - Frame, Dorothy L. (Box 81)
  - Friedman, Laura A. (Box 81)
  - Frothingham, Elizabeth (Box 81)
  - Galloway, Roberta B. (Box 81)
  - Gambrill, Elizabeth C. (Box 81)
  - Ganz, Chrysta H. (Box 81)
  - Gaston, Beatrice M. (Box 81)
  - Gibbs, Angelica S. (Box 81)
  - Gibson, Ruth (Box 81)
  - Gilbert, Beatrice (Box 81)
  - Gitchell, Helen K. (Box 81)
  - Goldthwaite, Hilda G., [EMPTY] (Box 81)
  - Gordon, Katharine (Box 81)
  - Graham, Jean (Box 81)
  - Gray, Elleanor (Box 81)
  - Griswold, Ruth M. (Box 81)
  - Gwynn, Sylvia (Box 81)
  - Hamilton, Miriam C. (Box 81)
  - Hanford, Gladys L. (Box 81)
  - Hanson, Louise (Box 81)
  - Hare, Annie C. (Box 81)
  - Harlan, Edith B. (Box 81)
  - Hartmann, Janet A. (Box 81)
  - Haskins, Helen (Box 81)
  - Hawes, Alice B. (Box 81)
  - Hazen, Abigail (Box 81)
  - Hebbard, Gertrude M. (Box 81)
  - Hellman, C. Doris (Box 81)
  - Hellman, Rhoda (Box 81)
  - Hicks, Ruth Ilsley (Box 81)
  - Hincks, Katrina E. (Box 81)
  - Hobby, Winifred R. (Box 81)
  - Hooper, Alice (Box 81)
  - Hosac, Constance (Box 81)
  - Howe, Margaret DeLancey (Box 81)
  - Hoysradt, Eleanor (Box 81)
  - Hughes, Ruth (Box 81)
  - Humphreys, Katharine E. (Box 81)
  - Humpstone, Nancy Elizabeth (Box 81)
  - Hunt, Dorothy (Box 81)
  - Hutsel, Rita H. (Box 81)
  - Hutton, Sara B. (Box 81)
  - Izzeddin, Nejla M. (Box 81)
  - Jargo, Lillian B. (Box 81)
  - Jaynes, Nancy Cheever (Box 81)
  - Jenkins, Nina M. (Box 81)
  - Jessup, H. Elizabeth D. (Box 81)
  - Jessup, Janet H. (Box 81)
  - Johnson, Abigail B. (Box 81)
  - Johnson, Evelyn (Box 81)
  - Johnston, Rebecca C. (Box 81)
  - Jones, Esther T. (Box 81)
  - Jones, Marie E. (Box 81)
  - Joy, Elsie Whitney (Box 81)
  - Judkins, Margaret N. (Box 81)
  - Kenderdine, Margaret H. (Box 81)
  - Kennedy, Ruth J. (Box 81)
  - Kerr, Jean M. (Box 81)
  - Kilborne, Elizabeth A. (Box 81)
  - Killam, Louise (Box 81)
  - King, Jane E. (Box 81)
  - Kingman, Celia C. (Box 81)
  - Kiser, Carolyn H. (Box 81)
  - Kluge, Alexandra (Box 81)
  - Kohn, Caroline M. (Box 81)
  - Kroll, Else A. (Box 81)
  - Lackner, Antoinette (Box 81)
  - Ladd, Vernon A. (Box 81)
  - Lanctot, Eleanor D. (Box 81)
  - Lasell, Nancy Manning (Box 81)
  - Law, Margaret B. (Box 81)
  - Learned, Emily B. (Box 81)
  - Lee, Frances (Box 81)
  - LeFevre, Frances (Box 81)
  - Litchfield, Elizabeth B. (Box 81)
  - Lloyd, Gwendolyn (Box 81)
  - Lowrie, Barbara F. (Box 81)
  - Ludwig, Margaret G. (Box 81)
  - MacLean, Elizabeth R. (Box 81)
  - Makepeace, Dorothy (Box 81)
  - Mallay, Helena (Box 81)
  - Mallery, Mary (Box 81)
  - Malloch, Elizabeth G. (Box 81)
  - Maltman, Martha R. (Box 81)
  - Mangan, Catherine DeLamater (Box 81)
  - May, Jean E. (Box 81)
  - Mays, Joy (Box 81)
  - McCain, Elizabeth E. (Box 81)
  - McCollough, Elizabeth (Box 81)
  - McDill, Jane R. (Box 81)
  - McGowin, Evelyn L. (Box 81)
  - McGrath, Marian E. (Box 81)
  - McGuirk, Elizabeth (Box 81)
  - McKee, Nancy J. (Box 81)
  - McLaren, Elizabeth (Box 81)
  - McLean, Sarah H. (Box 81)
  - Mead, Katherine L. (Box 81)
  - Michalik, Christina (Box 81)
  - Miller, Elizabeth W. (Box 81)
  - Miller, Sara C. (Box 81)
  - Mills, Isabel (Box 81)
  - Moffatt, Elizabeth P. (Box 81)
  - Moore, Fidelia Leverett (Box 81)
  - Morgan, Dorothy A. (Box 81)
  - Morris, Virginia (Box 81)
  - Morse, Mary F. (Box 81)
  - Moss, Mary-Louise (Box 81)
  - Mott, Eleanor C. (Box 81)
  - Munro, Dorothy C. (Box 81)
  - Murray, Mary C. (Box 81)
  - Myers, Alice (Box 82)
  - Nabil, Marzieh K. (Box 82)
  - Naylor, Alice (Box 82)
  - Nelson, Mary Elizabeth (Box 82)
  - Neuberger, Alice J. (Box 82)
  - Nichols, Jeannette B. (Box 82)
  - Norris, Rachel H. (Box 82)
  - North, Anna P. (Box 82)
  - Nottage, Marion (Box 82)
  - Oakes, Virginia P. (Box 82)
  - O'Neil, Margaret E. (Box 82)
  - Osgood, Ruth V. (Box 82)
  - Osmond, Margaret N. (Box 82)
  - Ottis, Laura F. (Box 82)
  - Patterson, Katharine (Box 82)
  - Perkins, Evelyn I. (Box 82)
  - Phillips, Mary T. (Box 82)
  - Platt, Catherine (Box 82)
  - Pond, Barbara (Box 82)
  - Porter, Marion L. (Box 82)
  - Poss, Eleanor S. (Box 82)
  - Potter, Mary H. (Box 82)
  - Pullman, Alice L. (Box 82)
  - Rafter, Constance M. (Box 82)
  - Raha, Gabriele Josefine (Box 82)
  - Reeve, M. Joy (Box 82)
  - Reynolds, Mary C. (Box 82)
  - Richards, Carolyn R. (Box 82)
  - Richards, Mary Theodora (Box 82)
  - Richey, Amytis (Box 82)
  - Rickard, Geraldine (Box 82)
  - Ripley, Wilberta (Box 82)
  - Roberts, Marian C. (Box 82)
  - Robertson, Virginia K. (Box 82)
  - Rohrig, Leilani (Box 82)
  - Rose, Barbara Patton (Box 82)
  - Rosenberg, Louise A. (Box 82)
  - Ross, Averell A. (Box 82)
  - Schimmel, Alice (Box 82)
  - Schueller, Dorothy A. (Box 82)
  - Sears, Esther (Box 82)
  - Seeler, Sidney P. (Box 82)
  - Shaeffer, Dorothy A. (Box 82)
  - Shambaugh, Stephanie (Box 82)
  - Shepherd, Katharine Y. (Box 82)
  - Sherer, Marguerite A. (Box 82)
  - Shireman, Margaret (Box 82)
  - Siewers, Helen L. (Box 82)
  - Slade, Hope (Box 82)
  - Slocum, Louise (Box 82)
  - Sluder, Martha G. (Box 82)
  - Smith, Martha W. (Box 82)
  - Smith, Mary P. (Box 82)
  - Smith, Priscilla (Box 82)
  - Smyth, Kathleen B. (Box 82)
  - Snyder, Alice P. (Box 82)
  - Sparrow, Margaret A. (Box 82)
  - Spear, Abbie-Louise (Box 82)
  - Spencer, Helen K. (Box 82)
  - Spencer, Sara K. (Box 82)
  - Spitzer, Lydia C. (Box 82)
  - Stebbins, Gay (Box 82)
  - Steeves, Imogene H. (Box 82)
  - Stewart, Katherine E. (Box 82)
  - Stickney, Marcia H. (Box 82)
  - Stivers, Elizabeth S. (Box 82)
  - Strasser, Anne (Box 82)
  - Stringfellow, Katherine D. (Box 82)
  - Strunsky, Frances I. (Box 82)
  - Stuart, Jessie (Box 82)
  - Taber, Helen S. (Box 82)
  - Tanzer, Caroline M. (Box 82)
  - Tarr, Louise (Box 82)
  - Tawes, Mary-Anne (Box 82)
  - Taylor, Doris K. (Box 82)
  - Taylor, Susan U. (Box 82)
  - Thesmacher, Pauline (Box 82)
  - Thompson, Caroline G. (Box 82)
  - Townsend, Frances (Box 82)
  - Tucker, Marguerite (Box 82)
  - Turney, E. Adelaide (Box 82)
  - Twyeffort, Dorothy W. (Box 82)
  - Upjohn, Esther (Box 82)
  - Vail, Rita J. (Box 82)
  - Van Saun, Janet W. (Box 82)
  - Van Siclen, Virginia (Box 82)
  - Verriere, Madeleine M. (Box 82)
  - von Tiling, Johanna E. (Box 82)
  - Voorhees, Florence E. (Box 82)
  - Walker, Margaret W. (Box 82)
  - Walling, Frederika C. (Box 82)
  - Walton, Ida-Patterson (Box 82)
  - Ward, Margaret M. (Box 82)
  - Warner, Agnes H. (Box 82)
  - Warren, Mary Amelia (Box 82)
  - Webster, Lillias D. (Box 82)
  - Wehrman, Margaret A. (Box 82)
  - Wells, Eleanor B. (Box 82)
  - Wells, Kathryn S. (Box 82)
  - West, Anne J. (Box 82)
  - Weyerhaeuser, Sarah M. (Box 82)
  - White, Marian (Box 82)
  - Whitmore, Frances P. (Box 82)
  - Whitney, Alice M. (Box 82)
  - Wiederman, Constance M. (Box 82)
  - Wilkinson, Jane (Box 82)
  - Willard, Frances E. (Box 82)
  - Willcox, Edith H. (Box 82)
  - Williams, Constance (Box 82)
  - Williams, Rachel M. (Box 82)
  - Wilson, Frances S. (Box 82)
  - Wilson, Harriet L. (Box 82)
  - Winslow, Anne (Box 82)
  - Woodard, Nancy (Box 82)
  - Woolsey, Elizabeth D. (Box 82)
  - Wuerthele, Virginia E. (Box 82)
  - Wylie, M. Elizabeth (Box 82)
  - Yarnelle, Elizabeth C. (Box 82)
  - Zeleny, Carolyn (Box 82)
  - Ziegler, Barbara E. (Box 82)
- Class of 1931
  - RESTRICTED (Boxes 83-86)
- Class of 1932
  - RESTRICTED (Boxes 86-90)
- Class of 1933
  - RESTRICTED (Boxes 90-93)
- Class of 1934
  - RESTRICTED (Boxes 93-96)
- Class of 1935
  - RESTRICTED (Boxes 97-100)
- Class of 1936
  - RESTRICTED (Boxes 101-104)
- Class of 1937
  - RESTRICTED (Boxes 105-108)
- Class of 1938 - Class of 1942
  - RESTRICTED (Boxes 109-124)
- Class of 1951 - Class of 1958, (28 boxes)
  - RESTRICTED